Privacy Policy of Dreamily
==========================

To use the services of Dreamily, you should read and comply with the Privacy Policy. The use of some features of Dreamily.ai requires you to open the following permissions.

·**Storage permission** (for storing information on the phone and for accessing the original content when the user continues to write the message)

·**Camera permission** (for the user to generate images to share and save images of the continuation content)

·**Microphone permission** (for users to make calls to characters)

**We use Mob Tech for the login and share function. Mob Tech may collect device attribute information of your ( anonymous device identifier (OAID), software list, advertising identifier IDFA) and device status information for security events investigation, for detecting and preventing fraudulent activity, as well as detecting and preventing network attacks and abuses to secure network security and operational security.**

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Dreamily.ai. We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at support@dreamily.ai.

When you visit our website (the "Website"), use our mobile application, as the case may be (the "App"), we appreciate that you are trusting us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what types of information we collect and under what circumstances the information is shared ,etc.. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy notice that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Services immediately. This privacy notice applies to all information collected through our Services (which, as described above, includes our Website and App).

Please read this privacy notice carefully as it will help you understand what we do with the information that we collect.

#### Scope of Application

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Services, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us. The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use.

When you use the Website or App's network services, we collect the data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Services. Depending on the device used, this data may include but not limited to information such as date, language used, time of access, hardware and software characteristics, and records of web pages you have requested on Dreamily. This data is for the purpose of Google Analytic and won't record any web page history other than visits to Dreamily.

When you use the service platform of "Dreamily" to engage in transactions, Dreamily will generate payment information such as your transaction order, the items you purchased, the amount you should pay and the payment method.

The payment is completed through third-party payment services provided by the cooperative third-party payment institution, and the third-party payment services may use biometric information for payment verification. Please read the privacy policy before using third-party payment services. If you do not agree with the terms, please stop using the third-party payment service.

To ensure the stable operation of the "Dreamily" service platform or to achieve related functions, we may utilize third-party software development kits (SDKs). As part of our efforts to protect data security, we will conduct strict security monitoring of the software development kits (SDKs) used by our partners. Our third-party SDKs are mostly used to meet the requirements of you and other users, so we may have to adjust them for new service requirements. In this description, we will provide you with the latest information on third-party SDKs we used. The following third-party SDKs are currently integrated with the "Dreamily" service platform:

| Type of service | Provider of service | Purpose of cooperation | Method of cooperation | Permission needs to be obtained | Collected data types | Privacy Policies of Service Providers |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| SDK for login and social service | Umeng Tongxin (Beijing) Technology Co., Ltd. | U-Verify smart authentication<br><br>Social sharing and social login | Provide aggregated login-sharing services for third parties | Achieve MAC addresses, unique device identifiers, applications list, and phone numbers | Identification data, network status information, serial number of the device | [https://www.umeng.com/policy](https://www.umeng.com/policy) |
| SDK for data analysis service | BytePlus Pte. Ltd. | Data discovery<br><br>Analyze user behavior data and app operation data to improve business growth, and monitor app stability and crash problems. | Embedding the third-party SDK that collects and transmits data | Achieve MAC addresses, unique device identifiers, and user actions in the App | Identification data, network status information | [https://docs.byteplus.com/legal/docs/privacy-policy](https://docs.byteplus.com/legal/docs/privacy-policy) |
| SDK for login and social service | MobTech | ShareSDK<br><br>Social sharing and social login | Provide aggregated login-sharing services for third parties | Achieve MAC addresses, unique device identifiers, applications list, and phone numbers | Device identifier data, location information, network information, SDK authentication related request results, cell phone number. Device information includes: device identifier (IMEI, IDFA, Android ID, MAC, OAID and other related information), application information (application crash information, notification switch status, software list and other related information, based on our service of detecting and implementing ID synchronization and merging links for you, we will obtain application list information), device parameters and system information (device type, device model, operating system and hardware related information). Network information includes: IP address, WiFi information, base station information and other related information.<br><br>The above information is also obtained in the background of the application. | [https://mob.com/about/policy](https://mob.com/about/policy) |
| SDK for text to speech service | Microsoft | Speech synthesis of AI output content | Embedding the third-party SDK | \-  | \-  | [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement) |
| SDK for tracking errors | Sentry | Real-time error tracking | Embedding the third-party SDK | Obtain information about running processes | Identification data, network status information | [https://sentry.io/privacy/](https://sentry.io/privacy/) |
| SDK for data analysis service | Firebase | Data discovery<br><br>Analyze user behavior data and app operation data to improve business growth, and monitor app stability and crash problems. | Embedding the third-party SDK that collects and transmits data | Achieve MAC addresses, unique device identifiers, and user actions in the App | Identification data, network status information | [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) |

#### Information Usage

We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, to enter or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.

1. To facilitate account creation and logon process. If you choose to link your account with us to a third-party account (such as your Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process for the performance of the contract.
    
    \- 1.1 When you register for a Single Sign On (SSO) account, the Google, Facebook and Twitter SDKs will be integrated and collected. The purpose of collecting these account information is to provide you with a better service through account management, so that you can synchronise your document data by logging in to your account and continue to use the information you have synchronised by logging in to your account when you change devices, without losing your data as a result of changing devices. The third party may be able to obtain your account information and other information you choose to provide depending on the permissions you grant.
    
    \- 1.2 When retrieving information from Google, Facebook and Twitter during the login process, we only obtain your profile, username and openID for account and personal data management.
    
    \- 1.3 Deactivate account: click on -"about"-"Deactivate my account", and then send an email to support@dreamily.ai including screenshot of homepage, username and reason for deactivating. We will review and deactivate your account within 10 working days, your personal data records will be deleted after account deactivation.
    
2. To provide the better personaliszed service. After obtaining your data, the software will upload it to the server for the sole purpose of optimizing the model and character network for your personal use so that you can make better use of the service.
    
3. Request feedback. We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.
    
4. To send administrative information to you. We may use your contact information to send you the product, service, and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.
    
5. To enforce our terms, conditions ,and policies for business purposes, to comply with legal and regulatory requirements ,or in connection with our contract.
    
6. To respond to legal requests and prevent harm. If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.
    
    **Information Share**
    
    We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations.
    
7. Consent: We will not use your information for purposes other than those specified in this agreement without your consent.
    
8. Performance of a Contract: Where we have entered a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.
    
9. Legal Obligations: We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal processes, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements)
    
10. Vital Interests: We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.
    
11. Service Optimization: To maintain the software's safety and enjoyment, we provide information and content to our service providers who support our business. These include cloud service providers and content moderation service providers, as well as service providers who help us market the software. In addition, in order to optimize and improve the Service, we work with analytics providers.
    
    **Information Storage and Transfer**
    
    We may transfer, store, and process your information in countries other than your own.
    
    The information you provide to us is kept as long as required by our contractual obligations or for the purpose of providing you with our services. Where your information is not required to provide the service, we retain it only if we have a legitimate business reason to do so, as permitted by applicable laws. However, it may be necessary to hold this data for a longer period of time if it is necessary to comply with our legal obligations or to establish, exercise, or defend legal claims.
    
    If you close your account, we will begin deleting data for which there is no justifiable business reason. You can request to be forgotten or to have your account data deleted if you live in a GDPR jurisdiction, we will respond as soon as possible. This decision may not be reversed.
    
    Our servers are located in the United States. If you are accessing our Services from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us in our facilities in the United States. In addition, we enabled the cloud server and the necessary information will be sent to Google Cloud.
    
    **Information Security**
    
    We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical security measures.
    
    We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. We are committed to safeguarding your personal information to the best of our abilities. Please be aware that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We encourage you to access the Services within a secure environment especially when you transmit personal information to and from our Services.
    
    We have put in place the proper organizational and technical protections to guarantee a level of security commensurate with the likelihood and severity of risks to your rights and freedoms and those of other users. These technical and organizational measures will be maintained and updated as necessary to enhance our overall security.
    
    We will occasionally include links to and from the websites of our partner networks and affiliates. Please be aware that when you click on a link to any of these websites, you are going to be subject to their individual privacy policies. We do not accept responsibility for the information collected by these websites. Before you submit any information to these websites, please read these policies carefully.
    
    Please protect your personal information and provide it to others only when necessary. If you discover that your personal information has been compromised, please email us immediately at support@dreamily.ai, so that we can take appropriate action.
    
    **For Younger Users**
    
    1\. Users under the age of 18 may not create their own accounts without their parents' or guardians' permission. You should have your parent or guardian review this policy carefully if you are a minor, and use our services or provide us information with their consent.
    
    2\. The protection of minors' personal information is of the utmost importance to us. We will only use, share, transfer, or disclose minors' personal information with parental or guardian consent, or as necessary to protect the child.
    
    3\. If we discover that we have collected personal information from children without obtaining verifiable parental consent, we will delete the data as soon as possible.
    
    **Changes to This Privacy Policy**
    
    rom time to time, we may update this privacy notice to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
    
    ColorfulClouds Tech.
    
    Sep 23, 2022
